A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of XX, XX-XX (bulk 2014-2017)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Secretary of XX, XX-XX (bulk 2014-2017)
The Library of Virginia
XX
XX cubic feet (XX boxes)
Virginia. Office of the Secretary of XX
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78. Privacy-protected information has been flagged and/or sealed, but not removed from the collection. Restricted information may include, but is not limited to: attorney-client privileged documents, medical information, social security numbers, and Department of Corrections inmate classification material.
Acquisition Information
Accession XX transferred by the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, 12 January 2018.
Historical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governor's top management team.
The office of the Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety was created on April 8, 1972. Originally, the Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety oversaw the State Highway Commission, Division of Motor Vehicles, Department of State Police, Highway Safety Division, Office of Emergency Services, Department of Military Affairs, Virginia State Crime Commission, and the Law Enforcement Officers Training Standards Commission. Since that time, the Office has undergone a series of administrative reorganizations. On April 12, 1976, the Legislature established separate secretariats for transportation and public safety, effective July 1, 1976. On July 1, 1984, the offices were again combined. Finally, the two became separate offices on February 22, 1990, and have remained separate in the years since.
The Secretary of Public Safety is a member of the Governor's Cabinet, is appointed by the governor, and is subject to confirmation by the General Assembly. Throughout Governor Terrence McAuliffe's term (2014-2018), the Secretary of Public Safety was responsible for the direction of, or had jurisdiction over, 10 state agencies and boards. The agencies and boards under the heading of the Secretary of Public Safety during the Warner administration are as follows: Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, Department of Correctional Education, Department of Corrections, Department of Criminal Justice Services, Department of Emergency Management, Department of Fire Programs, Department of Juvenile Justice, Department of Military Affairs, the Virginia Parole Board, and the Virginia State Police.
XX
Scope and Content
The Secretary of Public Safety and Homeland Security records consists of XX archival boxes and are divided into XX series. Series have been designated for Correspondence-Assigned State Agencies, Correspondence and Supporting Documentation-Office of the Secretary, XX. These records document the activities of the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety and Homeland Security, as well as the agencies and boards which fall under its heading, during the gubernatorial term Gov. Terrence McAuliffe (2014-2018).
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files - Assigned State Agencies, XX
Series II. Correspondence and Subject Files - Office of the Secretary, XX
Series III. XX
Series IV. XX
Series V. XX
Series VI. XX.
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Assigned State Agencies, XX-XX., Extent: XX cu. ft. (XX boxes) (Box 1-XX)
  The Correspondence and Subject Files - Assigned State Agencies series is housed in XX boxes and is arranged alphabetically by agency. This series contains topical files and correspondence with the following agencies and boards that operated under the Secretary of Public Safety and Homeland Security: Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, the Department of Corrections, the Department of Criminal Justice Services, the Department of Emergency Management, the Department of Fire Programs, the Department of Forensic Science, the Department of Juvenile Justice, the Department of Military Affairs, the Virginia Parole Board, and the Virginia State Police. May include with supporting material such as agendas, reports, policies, and presentations. The following state agencies and boards operated under the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety during the Kaine administration:
  The correspondence files contain mostly correspondence between the agencies and the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety regarding issues that affect that particular agency or board. References to budgetary matters, litigation, studies and reports, board appointments, and legislation are frequently found in this material. These files also provide supporting documentation and background information on many topics.
  Subject files
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Department of
    - Correspondence, 2013-2017, undated. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Administrative investigation, 2014. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Administrative investigation, 2015. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Committee on Virginia ABC Information Technology Systems, 2015 Sept 3. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Committee on Virginia ABC Information Technology Systems, 2017 Apr 24. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bureau of Law Enforcement, 2014-2015. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of Law Enforcement - Quarterly reports, 2015-2016. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Charlottesville location, 2014. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Initial briefing, 2014. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Law Enforcement Expert Panel Review - Final recommendations, undated. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Law Enforcement Expert Panel Review - Meeting, 2015 Aug 26. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Organization, 2014. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Plan to merge ABC Bureau of Law Enforcement with Virginia State Police, 2003. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Presentation to Senate Finance Public Safety Subcommittee, 2015 June 23. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Revenue enhancements, 2014. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Distillers Association, undated. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council
    - Audit Report, 2014. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - General, 2013-2014. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Corrections, Department of
    - Correspondence, 2014. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2015. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2016-2017. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Austin v. Clarke, 20. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Cannon v. Hull, 2016-2017. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Corrections, Board of - Appointments, 2017. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Corrections, Board of - Data and reports, 2016-2017. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Corrections, Board of - Meeting, 2017 July 19. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Corrections, Board of - Meeting, 2017 Aug 8. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Corrections, Board of - Meeting, 2017 Sept 20. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Corrections, Board of - Policy review (Death of inmates), 2017. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Corrections, Board of - Relevant code sections, 2017. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Corrections, Board of - Staffing, 2017. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - CORIS-LIDS, 2014. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - CRM, 2026. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Drug Courts, 2012, undated. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Electronic health records, 2014. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HB 815 implementation, 2016. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Health Care Cost Assesment Report, 2016. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - House Appropriations - Public Safety Committee, 2014 Apr 22. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Initiatives, 2014 Sept 8. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Juvenile offenders - Life without parole, undated. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Management Information Summary Annual Report, 2017 June 30. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Operations, 2016-2017. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Payment in lieu of taxes, 2016. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Porter v. Clarke, 2016. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Powhatan Correctional Center replacement, 2016-2017. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Presentation to Secretary, 2014 Sept 17. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Prison Rape Elimination Act (PREA), 2014. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Public Safety Officers, 2016-2017. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Restoration of Rights - Notes, 2016. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Restrictive Housing, 2015-2017. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Sheriffs, 2015. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - State Responsible Inmate Realignment Workgroup, 2015. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Correctional Enterprises, 2014. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Reentry Pilot Proposal, 2017. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Visitation policies, 2017. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Williams v. Muse, 2014. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Department of
    - Correspondence, 2014. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2015. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Blueprints for Change, 2013-2015. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Blueprints for Change - Criminal Justice Issues, Firearms, 2014. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Coming Home to Work Program (Charlottesville), undated. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Community policing, 2016-2017. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Court appointed special advocates, 2015. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Crime Victims' Rights - Courtroom, 2017. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Criminal justice reform, 2015-2017. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative, 2014. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Capacity Building Training, 2014 Nov 3-7. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Communications Workgroup, 2017 July 11. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Correspondence and applications, 2014 Oct. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Data and Information Work Team, 2016 Apr 22. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Planning Committee, 2014 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Planning Committee, 2014 June 26. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Planning Committee, 2014 July 23. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Planning Committee, 2014 Aug 28. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Planning Committee, 2014 Sept 8. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Planning Committee, 2014 Oct 23. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Planning Committee, 2014 Dec 8. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Planning Committee, 2015 Jan 6. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2015 Apr 9. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2015 May 12. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2015 June 19. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2015 Sept 22. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2015 Oct 27. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2015 Nov 30. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2016 Mar 22. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2016 Apr 19. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2016 May 27. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Policy Team, 2017 Mar 7. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Steering Committee, 2014 July 23. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Steering Committee, 2014 Spet 29. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Evidence Based Decision Making Initiative - Workshop, 2015 June 22-23. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Governor's budget amendment, undated. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Grant awards, 2016. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Guide for Developing Housing for Ex-Offenders (1 of 2), 2004. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Guide for Developing Housing for Ex-Offenders (2 of 2), 2004. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Initial briefing, 2014 Jan. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Integrated Criminal Justice System web portal, 2015. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Jail Mental Health Pilot Program, 2016-2017. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Jail/Prison reentry data, undated. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Justice Policy Institute - The Billion Dollar Divide, Virginia's Sentencing, Corrections and Criminal Justice System, 2014. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Law Enforcement and Community Relations listening session, 2016 Sept 27. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Law enforcement officer training, 2015-2017. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Local Re-entry Councils, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Local / Regional Jails - Inmate Mental Health Services, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Mandatory training and conference fees, 2017. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - National Criminal Justice Association, 2015 Dec 2-4. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Offender re-entry, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Presentation to Secretary, 2015 June 12. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Pretrial Risk-bases Decision Making, 2013 Dec. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Pretrial Services / Community Corrections, 2017. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Report on Current and Projected Status of Federal, State, and Local Funding for Victim Witness Protection Programs, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - School and Campus Safety, Governor's Task Force on, 2013-2014. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - School and Camput Safety - Publications, 2015. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Statewide Strategic Criminal Justice Plan, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Victims Services, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Community Criminal Justice Association, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Management, Department of
    - Correspondence, 2014-2017. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Continuity of Government Plan, 2017. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Critical information requirements, undated. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Emergency Operation Plan - Executive Order 41, undated. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Emergency Shelter Capabilities and Readiness, 2016. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - FirstNet - Virginia Public Safety Broadband, 2017. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Flooding, 2016-2017. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Hampton Roads, 2014-2017. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Hurricane Planning and Preparedness, 2014. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Hurricane Planning and Preparedness - Evacuation and lane reversal, 2016. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - In Season Hurricane Review Report, 2014. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - State Disaster Funding / City of Richmond - Decision brief, 2017. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Threat Hazard Identification and Risk Analysis (THIRA) - Presentation, 2017 July 17. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Tiered Hurricane Evacuation briefing, 2017 May 11. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Unmanned Aircraft Systems, 2015-2016. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Unmanned Aircraft Systems - Overview and Next Steps - Presentation, 2017 Feb 1. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Fire Programs, Department of
    - Correspondence, 2014-2016. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Forensic Science, Department of
    - Correspondence, 2015-2017. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Annual reports, 2014-2015. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - DNA Notification Project, 20014. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Drug cases submitted to DFS, undated. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Forensic Science Training for Attorneys and Judges, 2017 Aug 16. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Forensic Training Stakeholder meeting, 2017 Oct 23. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Hair microscopy, 2016-2017. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Initial briefing, 2014 Jan. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Justice Commission, 2014. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Legislation, 2016. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Legislation - Victim Confidentiality (HB 373), 2016. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Monthly meetings, 2014. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Notice regarding controlled substances workload, 2017. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Overview - Forensic Science 101, 2014. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Policy changes, 2014-2016. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Post-conviction DNA testing, 2017. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Scientific Advisory Committee, 2014. (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Senate Finance Committee presentation, 2016 May 18. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Strategic planning, 2014-2015. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Update, 2016 June 6. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Juvenile Justice, Department of
    - Correspondence, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Adult Inmate Mentoring Proposal, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Annie E. Casey Foundation, 2015. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Annual review, 2015. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Board expiration, 2017. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Bon Air Juvenile Correctional Center, 2015. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Budget reduction issues, 2014 Jan. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Chesapeake facility, 2017. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Data Resource Guide, 2013. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Data Resource Guide, 2016. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Dominion solar proposal, undated. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Education Task Force presentation/town hall, 2016 Aug 23. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Education programs in secure environments, 2016. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Initial briefing, 2014 Jan. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Juvenile Life Without Parole (LWOP), 2016. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Length of stay, 2015. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Mental Health Services - Special populations (Workgroup #3), 2015 July 1. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Personnel data - presentation, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - PEW Charitable Trusts, 2014. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Post-secondary education options, 2011. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Programs and partners, 2016. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Proposal for change, 2014. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Redeveloped business operations model and facility plan, 2013. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Reentry to Education and Employment Program (REEP), 2014. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Regulatory concerns, undated. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Regulatory non-compliance, 2014. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Reorganization chart, 2014. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Retention plan (BJCC), 2016. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - School discipline for students with disabilities, 2016. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - School to Prison Pipeline - Keeping kids in classrooms, not courtrooms, 2015. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Senate Finance Public Safety Subcommittee presentation, 2014 Aug 26. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Six month re-arrests for JCC release, 2016. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Strategic planning, 2015. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Transformation, 2015-2016. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Transformation, 2015-2016. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Transformation, 2017. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Transformation - Budget, 2015. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Transformation - Juvenile Justice Population Outcomes, undated. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Weekly meetings, 2014. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Work/Education Release Program (WERP), 2015. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Military Affairs, Department of
    - Correspondence, 2015-2016. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Camp Pendleton - Decision brief, 2016. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - National Guard Counterdrug Activities Plan, 2015. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Quadrennial Review, 2017. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Parole Board
    - Correspondence, 2013-2017. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Agenda, 2016 May 16. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Assistance from the Dept. of Corrections, 2016. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Budget reduction strategy, 2014. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Governor's Commission on Parole Review, 2016. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Governor's Commission on Parole Review - Final Report and Recommendations, 2015 Dec. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Initiatives and obstacles, 2017. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Special Investigation Unit, 2016. (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Statistics and Related Trends, 2016. (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Statutes and reports, 2016-2017. (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - State Responsible Offender Profile, 2016. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Virginia State Police
    - Correspondence, 2014. (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 2015-2017. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Accomplishments, 2017. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Asset forfietures, 2014-2015. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Briefing, 2014 Aug 12. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 2014-2017. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Progress Report on the Uniform Prevention and Safety Program, 2015. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Statistical Summary of Narcotics Enforcement, 2013. (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, XX-XX., Extent: XX-XX cubic feet (XX boxes). (Box X-X)
  The Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary series is housed in XX boxes.
  - Correspondence, 2013 Dec. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Constituent, 2014. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2014 Jan-Apr. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2014 May-Aug. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2014 Sept-Dec. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2015 Jan-May. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2015 June-Sept. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2015 Oct-Dec. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2016 Jan-Mar. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2016 Apr-Dec. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2017. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, undated. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Invitations, 2014. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Invitations, 2015-2016. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Invitations declined, 2014-2015. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 2014-2017. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Accomplishments, 2016. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Accomplishments, 2017. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Agency accomplishments, 2017. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Agency head meeting, 2014 June 17. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Agency head meeting, 2014 Aug 25. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Agency head meeting, 2016 Apr 28. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Agency head meeting, 2017 May 16. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Agency updates, 2016. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Agency updates, 2017. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 2013-2014. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Annual agency meeting, 2015. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Annual report brainstorming session, undated. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Anti-marijuana groups, 2015. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Archiving records, 2017. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Attorney General briefing, 2014. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, undated. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Autism community, 2017. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Board recommendations, 201. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Briefing binder, 2016 July-Aug. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet briefing on 2015 hurricane season, 2015. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cabinet continuity, undated. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cabinet on the Road - Public Safety Roundtable, 2016. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Capital Outlay Projects - Annual Progress Report, 2015. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Capital Outlay Projects - Annual Progress Report, 2017. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Connections, 2016. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Caroline County - Community Profile, undated. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Civil disturbance, 2016. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Coalition for Justice for Dustin Turner, 2014. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Campaign, 2014. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Confirmation Prep Session - Governor-elect Terrence R. McAuliffe, Common Ground, 2014 Jan 6. (Box 18, Folder 14)